https://www.westarfcu.com/privacy-policy/

Annual Meeting
It’s Not Banking, It’s Personal!
Lorem ipsum dolor sit
amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.
FACTS
WHAT DOES WESTAR FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO
WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
– Social Security number and checking account information
– credit history and employment information
– income and payment history
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Westar Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Westar Federal Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes –
to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
We don’t share
Questions?
Call 315-672-7827315-672-7827 or go to www.westarfcu.com
What we do
How does Westar Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Westar Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
– open an account or apply for a loan
– show your government-issued ID or provide employment information
– give us your contact information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
– sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes
– information about your creditworthiness
– affiliates from using your in formation to market to you
– sharing for non affiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
– Westar Federal Credit Union has no affiliates
Non affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
– Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies, government agencies, plastic card processors (credit/debit/ATM), financial statement publishers or printers, mailhouse, consumer reporting agencies, data processors, and check/share draft printers
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
– Our joint marketing partners include CUNA Mutual Group’s MEMBERCONNECT, credit card companies, and loan recapture programs
Contact Us
Westar Federal Credit Union2565 Hambletonian Way, Camillus, NY 13031-0060
Address: P.O. Box 60, Camillus, NY 13031-0060Routing Number: 221380842Westar Federal Credit Union NMLS ID# 806577Karen Grabowski NMLS# 1137898Lucinda Kraus NMLS# 1804423
Lisa Lamanna NMLS# 421990
Phone: 315-672-7827  315-672-7827 | Fax: 315-672-9282Toll-Free: 1-844-573-8190 Email: westar@westarfcu.com
Lending Email: lending@westarfcu.com
Follow Us
Follow our student branch
Online Banking Bill Pay Questions Call: 1-855-276-1965
Visa Debit Card Activation/PIN Change: 1-800-992-3808 Lost or Stolen Debit Card: 1-800-554-8969 Lost or Stolen Credit Card: 1-800-543-5073 International lost/stolen Credit Card: 727-570-4881 International lost/stolen Debit Card: 614-564-5101
Business Hours are Monday – Friday 9:00 AM – 5:00 PM
View our holiday schedule for a list of closures.
Disclosures
See our Privacy Policy
See our Fee Schedule
See our Master Membership Account Agreement
See our Truth in Savings Disclosure for Share/Savings Accounts
See our Truth in Saving Disclosure for Draft/Checking Accounts
See the Patriot Act Disclosure
Federally Insured by NCUA
